all right I'm going to roll through the
12 exercis in this program the first
one's a squat you're just going to put
your arms like this come down all the
way come back up very straightforward if
you can't go rock bottom just go to
parallel next exercise is a single leg
RDL uh it's Single Leg reaching RDL so
I'm going to keep this leg locked into
place if you squeeze this glute it it'll
come back a little bit lock it into
place go like that come back
up the goal is to get a big stretch in
that hamstring okay next exercise the
hip thrust you can do this off of a
bench or a
couch put your arms like this come down
come up come down make sure you come all
the way up by squeezing your
glutes okay next exercise band seated
hip abduction double Loop the band put
your legs through I keep the band right
underneath my
legs and just come out squeeze come back
in just like that all right next
exercise the reverse lunge I'm just
going to step back come back up notice
this knee almost touches the ground I
lean forward slightly and sink down into
that hip next exercise rkc plank I'm
going to get in a plank position and
squeeze my glutes just like this okay
I'm going to plank squeeze the
glutes you will get a posterior pelvic
tilt by squeezing the
glutes next exercise single leg hip
thrust again this can be done off of a
bench or a couch I seated I pick one leg
up come up squeeze come down come up
squeeze
next exercise is a sideline clam raise
this
one I'm going to get in a sideline
position my hips are flexed I'm bent I
come up all the way just like
this both legs rise
up next exercise is the Bulgarian split
squat I am going to put my back foot on
a chair a bench a couch whatever I I'm
leaning forward slightly so most of my
weight is on this leg I sink back and
down just like this sink into this hip
come back
up most of my weight is on this leg this
leg is just for balance all right next
exercise the lateral Band Walk I'm going
to put my feet like
this I going going to pull this tight
get down into a slightly crouched
position and just go side to side like
this next exercise is the reverse
hyper this one I'm just going to drape
across something a bench a table
something like that a couch something I
to grab onto and squeeze the
glutes notice I'm the spine stays pretty
neutral and the motion is mostly at the
hips with the glutes
squeezing and the last exercise is the
sideline hip raise this is like the clam
raise except I am not
flexed my body is in a straight position
just like
this hope you like the challenge